Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love Be erased or let it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Oh, so you can smack that ass and give it a BDL since you heard it.
You think you want to be like Kim Kardashian, sit your ass down.
You talk about me and sound like a clown.
If I can get you hyped up, if I can get you on the panel and I can get you riled up,
if I can get my fucking pussy ass and I get you fucking cracked up, I'm good.
Peace out.
West Coast, yo.
What is the next fucking rhyme?
Where is Mikey at?
It's left out
So I want to rap battle you trash
You trash. I want to rap battle. There's nothing more to say. Your shit is fucking like it's like it sounds like the same shit
You're fucking wrapped about every day. I fucking come and I fucking make motherfucking gay for our pay
Okay
Correct come with the fucking like the current events talk with the fucking chat
Learn how to fucking yeah
Not some wacky the ass fucking shit that you fucking wrap all the fucking time on every fucking panel
Show us how you fucking manhandle you
Word so when I come correct all I have to say is when you rap you sound like you slack. I came through I told you again
Black bear on a fucking wall. You're just dumb as fuck and you just fucking yeah
You fucking think you got fucking voice cuz you're fucking black
I would have a better fucking voice. I'm white and I can rap and better fucking do better verse
You're so stupid fucking blonde bird fucking golden girl. I will fucking bend you over and make you fucking hurl. Oh hell no
You must be crazy you see talking about you. Why it's too easy you white bitches love me
That's why I gave y'all the BBC. So who gives a fuck what you talking about when you rapping against me?
I trash you out in the motherfucking world so you can understand me
I'm a king why you want to mess with me put you down and see you guys
Understand you know what a mess with me
Fuck you
Okay, okay bronze bird. We heard what you fucking said and it was all fucking dumb like a fucking bird
And that's gonna get fucking bird flu and it's gonna fall down on a tree like a fucking voodoo
I'm gonna fucking put a fucking voodoo on your motherfucking ass that bird black bird ass is gonna get grass
Yo, you look at that board you look mad bored when I look at your avatar when I did the zoom
And matter of fact, you still trash. It's like Jim next room
Shout out
Makes me you fucking wanna rock the way the way I make people rap is I fucking make people fucking go
Cataract I make them fucking want to fucking get and turn
Attention. Yeah, so so check side at two balls
So the way that you rap, it makes you want to earl.
And the way that you talk, it sounds like you want to be a valley girl.
Why are you faking this?
Oh my god, I'm a fucking valley girl.
I'm gonna fucking earl on your fucking penis, because it was so small and immediate.
Oh my god, I don't want to see this.
Oh my god. I don't know. It was a black guy, but he was so fucking mean. I was expressing
your fucking huge ass when I got a little penny.
Yo, so when you talk, yo, all I have to say is like, I keep telling you that you trash.
How the fuck are you Persian related to Kim Kardashian? You have no ass.
Listen, Kim. Kim. Kim Kardashian can fucking lick my fucking flat ass. She's fucking not Persian. She's Armenian and she fucking got her shit from fucking Ray J with the sex video tape.
Wait, where are you going? Stop it.
That was the way I was going to show you. I wasn't surprised.
Yeah, I'm surprised you beat his rapping.
It makes me want to hurt more than she even expressed.
Let me see. I haven't done a song for you.
I was trying to make the video, but it's too slow.
If you're still there.
If not, I'll have to tell you to come back to the show.
This is not too personal.
So shattered skies
With nothing left
But haunted hearts
A thousand no's
A million tries
Still Johnny's name
Was in my cries
Every fall became
Don't
cuter being patriot or me? Who's Sean Ballantyne? Also, what is what is going on in these clips?
I don't know. Hold on, I'm gonna play this one again. I'll play the other version.
I don't want to put that on very good. I just she just came back and I was like
I should have wanted to, yeah, you got it.
I tried to do the video, but the video is not co-operative.
But you have the audio.
Matthew the bigger picture
I like that.
But you know what, and you inspire me to go blonde, I think.
This is a good look from here.
I'm just going to do it as a video feature, OK?
Yeah, so I had this service where I could make clips out
of my old shows, and so this was months and months ago
we had this rap battle.
But I'm not gonna do more of the wrap-out. The wrap-out was pretty terrible
That's what else was on that. It was
Interesting things. Wow
If panelists click slide, let's see. It's is fucking making me irate
Fuck you at man
I will go dyke if I stay on the panel for another motherfucking minute
Yo, shout out to chat yo, and let me tell y'all something
The blonde bird doesn't know how to fucking be lit. I'm always lit. He's quitting you son whether beta was
Wait, wait a white person and this guy's black
And she did a good job at fucking China battle with this like guy with a bird emoji
And she took the W. Yeah
You lost though. I did I won. No, you lost you took an L. Yes there. You already like miles ahead
Yeah
who is it really? Because, yeah, and who were they talking about? Was she talking about
Bronzeberg with the bird emoji? Or me with the bird emoji? I don't know, maybe I'm just
too sensitive? But, for once I agreed with Bronzeberg, that wasn't L for, um, to be the
So so you can smat that ass and give it a big yell since you're a person
You think you wanna be like Kim Kardashian, sit your ass down
You talk about me, you sound like a clown
If I can get you hyped up, if I can get you on the panel and I can get you riled up
If I can get my fucking pussy ass and I get you fucking cracked up
I'm good, peace out
West Coast, yo
What is the next fucking rhyme?
Where is Nike at?
Bitch
So I want to rap battle you trash
Good trash. I wanted to rap battle. There's nothing more to say. Your shit is fucking like it's like it sounds like the same shit
You're fucking wrapped about every day. I fucking come and I fucking make motherfucking gay for our pay
Okay
Come with the fucking like current events, talk with the fucking chat, learn how to fucking
yap, not some wacky ass fucking shit that you fucking rap all the fucking time on every
fucking panel.
Show us how you fucking man handle.
You word.
So when I come correct, all I have to say is when you rap, you sound like you slack.
I came through.
I told you again.
I mean this is kind of like shocking that it's like
Or where was I I probably couldn't handle listening to them rap
I mean, I mean, I'm sorry. I know people are wanting to leave now because they're here even though it's like
They're just listening to the words they're saying
What are you at man?
Psyche
Cat lady is calling for you. I got a fucking job, Mike. This bitch is fucking making me irate
Fuck you at man. I will go dyke if I stay on the panel for another motherfucking minute
Yo, shout out to chat yo, and let me tell y'all something
He quit, he quit, he quit
Cause Bond Bird doesn't know how to fucking be lit
I'm always lit
He's quitting
You suck
Whatever
Beto is
Wait, wait a white person and this guy's black
And she did a good job at fucking China battle with this like guy with a bird emoji
And she took the W you lost though. I did
Okay
Not me, I'm shadow band again
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pro-mutual mic
Then boom, drop a bass line dirtier than the chat
Bum, bum, bum
Coast is crashing out
Smashing rafters like vows
Canada dries, they can watch cattle
Threatening people from an undisclosed stage
Natalie being backfired behind head
Mods praying, Lord, not again
Welcome to the Paniverse, baby
Hold your ground where the chaos hums
Like a feedback sound, we don't know who's sane
Who's banned or blessed, but the vibes unholy
And always possess
Scotty causing from the bone
Brags, he just dropped a cosmic load
Some sleep
And it's all so true.
Ghost is connected.
Canada drive timed out.
Randall's still typing.
Wait to be there just ban me.
Laughter static cat me out.
In stream noise.
You know what, I look at one of those.
You ever see that?
that woman and she was like you know looking for love with her on VH1 and she's like I forgot what she was there and she's either
porn star or something she was like
It's like oh, no, she's like she's like a musician or something
but you know it's like and then um and
One of her dates was like these sweet these like Swedish triplets. I think and they're all like they all look like this
They were like, huh, what's up? What's up? Yeah, we just we just wish you triplets. I can find them sometime
Yeah, that was your song I
Made a few tarot songs like um, and I don't know people are like
Because that's all my minus errors, it's my party
Looking for the tarot song they're called the priestess
Hold on, I hate looking for stuff because I'm always like,
I think we're not open-ended.
Sweet dog.
Okay, let's speed.
Spread the cards by candlelight
And shaking nights to
The high priestess beneath mortal disguise
Moonlight veiled immortal
Across the table
In street clothes, preaching mystery, and sermons of touch
Breaking the very vows you once imposed
The unspoken archana
She's the priestess, keeper of the tide
He's the hierophant gatekeeper of pride
Two paths of spirit crossing lines, they drew
He taught the temple, she taught what's true
Love became a cipher, neither could he code
Secrets turned sacred, sacred turned cold
It's just fate turned up, seeing every kiss was a heresy
The major organ is fine
They learn the secret, every mystic fears
Truth demands the death of what appears
She turned the veil, he dropped the crown
Two divine liars finally bowing down
The unspoken arcana
Ha, ha, ha
She's the priestess car
The lovers who rewrote the spine of time
The secret for the few who can read the air
And you'll be able to watch the lecture.
It's very interesting.
Watch the lecture.
Oh, it's not.
Yeah, it's going to be called the Web of Jezebel.
But I think you're supposed to do this for me last night.
I think I'm going to better watch it.
In the city of mirrors and a smile
A psyche walks where the ghost lights choke
Every face unmask, every word a spell
Every promise spun in the web of Jezebel
Bandits whisper blessings, thieves wear crowns
The prophets lost their maps to these haunted towns
He's been bound by silk, by sin, by code
But his spirit still burns down every...
In the web of Jezebel he almost disappears, but the panther comes, all teeth and tears, shadow mercy, eyes like nighter, cuts the cords, brings him back to life, he survived the cryptids, the narcissist charm, the psychopath's grin, the false alarm, the soul don't break, it just transcends, the web dissolves.
The story bends
He's dance with fever shirt why
He almost
The story bends
Every color's a key
Every tear or coat
Every death or rebirth
On the winding road
And the panther whispers
In a voice so low
They can't kill
presentation it's like so good and I don't like to like say like you know I
can't I could probably do just as good as one but it probably hit largely based
on this again these show you some interest I can show you something from
this video
This woman, then she has like this thing.
You know that, they have like those selfie cameras, right?
Like they put like a little graphic over like the face,
like with the glasses on it.
Well, it made like a face out of her neck.
Like there was like a face peering on her neck.
I don't know, or like her throat kind of thing.
And then I feel like it might throw,
I have a face there too, and it's kind of disturbing.
If you were like your Adam's apple,
mine is like humongous.
I do. I mean, I can look at it for a little bit, too.
Okay, so, there's a good channel.
Did you know a good show? I mean, you could get something out of this.
I think you'll like it. Set up all kinds of
political stuff. Let's see.
Blood rituals and things. I see it. It was about a year ago.
Let's see.
Delilah's dance, the recalculation, which is a little...
Okay, well let's check this out.
The one to control the clothes.
Do you want me to sing a letter for my screen name?
Oh, okay.
Yes, why C-H-E?
Let me do something.
I'm in glory, though.
Well, his friends and family mourn the loss of 17-year-old Caleb White.
This story has touched so many people all over the country.
It's just such a shocking case.
He was a star athlete in great shape.
It's really hard to understand how he could just collapse and pass away.
Yeah, you know, we all want to think that we would see the signs of something like this
and be able to prevent it.
But I spoke to a cardiologist today who says, if Caleb passed away from sudden cardiac
Tamar Hamlin's collapse on national TV in January shocked the country. He suffered sudden cardiac death.
Thankfully, he was resuscitated. Then last month, LeBron James' 18-year-old son, Brownie, collapsed on the USC campus.
He was also resuscitated. Then last week, 17-year-old Caleb White. Sadly, emergency medical teams were not able to bring him back.
Cardiologist Dr. Tom Egan says the most common cause is congenital. It's called hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.
You can see an increased risk of that disease.
Hypnosis is usually induced by a procedure known as a hypnotic induction involving a
series of preliminary instructions and suggestions. Operation Mockingbird, the CIA program consisted
of literally paying off editors and reporters at most mainstream news outlets. The New York Times,
When you cross the mainstream entertainment industry, who are in the boredom killing business,
with a military industrial complex, who are in the people killing business.
The Washington Post, Newsweek, A.P.
Operation Mockingbird 2.0
A suspense-filled, action-packed comedy-horror social engineering project
that will entertain you to death.
Sudden cardiac death.
Circus Maximus.
They clone Tyrone. It's a new movie on Netflix.
One of the top three movies in the world.
On Netflix right now was directed and co-written by a
filmmaker from Tuskegee.
The Tuskegee experiment. It started in 1932.
Hundreds of black men were recruited for what they thought
was free medical care.
a film maker from Tuskegee.
Jewel Taylor was born in Tuskegee
and later moved to Montgomery.
In his latest project, they cloned Tyrone.
They cloned Tyrone, stars Jamie Foxx,
and there's a sci-fi comedy streaming right now on Netflix.
Bread and Circuses, Psyops and Sightings, close to 5,000 documents, disclosure and disinformation, previously classified, house oversight and accountability subcommittee held a historic hearing on unidentified anomalous phenomena, also known as UFOs.
Lawmakers on Capitol Hill are digging into the national security concerns and the mystery posed by unidentified anomalous phenomena or UAPs.
also known as UFOs.
Do you believe that our government is in possession of UAPs?
Absolutely, based on interviewing over 40 witnesses over four years.
I know the exact locations.
A whistleblower who formerly worked on the Defense Department's UAP task force, David Grosh.
Biologics came with some of these recoveries.
Were they, I guess, human or non-human biologics?
Non-human, and that was the assessment of people
Psyops and sightings brought to you by the masters of misdirection and sleight of hand
Corporate America is bringing Satanism to the mainstream in
Preparation for the real disclosure when that man of sin is revealed
Let no man deceive you by any means
For that day shall not come except there come a falling away first and
That man of sin be revealed the son of perdition
Is that KFC chicken sandwich spicy?
Sinfully.
I do anything for one.
Anything?
Got you one.
Order any KFC sandwich online till July 2 for Diablo 4 reward.
Yeah!
Do not attempt to eat this burger unless you like sweating,
gasping, and jalapeno, avanero, and pepper jack cheese
and do salucinations.
My rules, members, sit your mouth on fire
with a one-time L Diablo single for 666
from the Carl's Jr. F.
Yeah!
If you ever heard of a real witch, so many demons are trapping them inside cans of water.
Inside this very warehouse sits the entire inventory of liquid-debt mountain water.
A lot of what I practice can be considered traditional witchcraft.
What you're about to witness is very real, very dangerous, and in my opinion, a terrible idea.
We enter into the dark half of the year.
Now is the time of the dead. I ask you spirits, those who are listening, I invite you here.
I offer this water as a vessel.
Now, for obvious reasons, we are not going to play the entirety of this ritual invocation.
But note, the date of this summon scene was October 2020.
And though they want you to take this commercial as a tongue-in-cheek joke, since it aired, there has been massive spikes in excess deaths.
and many of these casualties had been caused by liquid death in one form or another.
I welcome you.
Now is the time of the dead.
Demon-infused liquid death.
If you drink it, will you become possessed?
brought to you by Pfizer.
Satanism is becoming more popular.
We see a lot of TV shows geared towards the whole concept of, you know, very dark, satanic,
witchcraft-oriented sort of TV, and we see how a whole counterculture of teenagers
who are becoming more interested in this and growing popularity than because of it.
industrialized devil worship.
The hierarchy of paranormal multi-dimensional luminaries
are no longer content to govern from the shadows.
The first steps to real disclosure are underway.
A suspect described as a demon and an ogre is in custody
in connection to the New York Yolgo Beach killings.
You see, the rebellious nations have already chosen their path.
and the value of decision.
Choose now.
Is it the good book or a bad book?
According to one Utah school district, the Bible contains scriptures that are too violent
and too vulgar for young children, so it's now banned.
And even as they did not like to retain God in their knowledge, God gave them over to the
This afternoon, the After School Satan Club held its first-ever summer club at the Berm
County Public Library. Iris Chebelle Acevedo spoke with the campaign director to learn more about
what the club is all about.
The club was able to mea
in the southern tier in m
expressed interest in the
club. So they launched th
a contemporary art gallery in Minnesota recently held what it described as a quote,
demon summoning session. The free event was part of the Walker Art Center's Plant Teacher's Day
and author made an exhibit on how to trap a demon. Part of it instructed people to text the word
But I say that the things which the Gentiles sacrifice they sacrifice to devils and not to God
And I would not that ye should have fellowship with devils
You cannot drink the cup of the Lord and the cup of devils
You cannot be partakers of the Lord's table and of the table of devils
Devils
because they chose to follow in the hoof print of the fallen.
The shadow of death is enveloping the earth,
waiting for the sun to rise,
swallowing every soul that lies in its path.
Well, his friends and family mourn the loss of 17-year-old Caleb White.
This story has touched so many people all over the country.
It's just such a shocking case.
He was a star athlete in great shape.
It's really hard to understand how he could just collapse and pass away.
A star on and off the football field in the eyes of friends and family, 19-year-old mid-American
Nazarene student athlete Maizel Law.
He collapsed during a practice and died hours later.
they can be no. Legendary Houston rapper big pokey is died after fainting on
stage last night. Videos circulating on social media show the sitting sideways
rapper collapsed on stage during a show in Beaumont last night. He was 48 years
old.
Former Cal All-American wide receiver Sean Dawkins died suddenly yesterday at the age
of 52.
In the early 90s, he was one of the best wide receivers in college football, earning consensus.
First team All-American honors following his junior season in 1992.
A few months later, the Indianapolis Colts made Dawkins the 16th overall selection in
the NFL Draft, and it was with the Colts that Dawkins made his mark as one of the most consistent
in the league. He was a devoted husband, father, and friend. He is survived by his wife and
two young twin daughters.
The KD community is remembering a high school cheerleader. Her parents are
sitting down for an interview after they say she suffered cardiac arrest at
a cheer camp. Her mother will never forget the moment the cheer coach called
from the camp they were attending at Texas A&M. They learned that same coach
had performed CPR on Cali. If it wasn't for Everly, we would have never had the
chance to say goodbye.
Right now to the tragic and sudden death of a 10-year-old cheerleader in Southfield sending shockwaves through her family and the community
The Oakland County medical examiner is trying to figure out what caused this young girl to pass away
It's like a nightmare to watch a kid go so soon.
Nothing I've never seen in my life. It was just after 8 o'clock Friday night outside the school in Southfield where they were practicing
were told Monet collapsed 911 was called and someone started CPR. Paramedics arrived quickly, but Monet wasn't breathing.
And despite life-saving measures, she never regained consciousness. The 10 year old was later pronounced dead at the hospital.
New Mexico State University announced that one of its student athletes died suddenly
on Monday morning. Talia Chaviria, a member of the NMSU women's soccer team, died on Monday
according to the university. 20 years old and was set to enter her junior year at New
Mexico State, a shining light within the team according to NMSU's head coach.
Former University of Iowa football player Cody Ince died this weekend. The 23-year-old was an offensive lineman for the Hawkeyes from
2019 to 2021. He passed away unexpectedly near his home in Grantsburg, Wisconsin.
According to the online obituary, he leaves behind his fiance, parents, sister and other family.
Tim Kennedy was well known and Wilmington's creative and cultural arts community. He passed away unexpectedly at just 55 years old.
Kennedy was an actor, dancer, director, and mentor to many people.
sudden death among healthy working-age people worldwide is skyrocketing here in
America it was up 40% our next guest contends a 10% jump would have been a
one and two hundred year event but this was 40% cause unknown the epidemic has
sudden deaths tell us about some of these unexpected sudden deaths it seems
like there are a lot of them I mean just but from a Google search you can find
like a lot of 12 14 16 18 year olds that are just dropping dead suddenly tell
Right. And in my book, I talk about sudden death, and we look at the sudden deaths of athletes,
which, you know, did it happen before 21? It did. There was a study in 2006 by the
Los Saint Institute in Switzerland that showed over the course of 38 years, they found 1101
sudden athletic deaths, which is about 29 a year globally. We'd be lucky to have a month with just
29 since 2021. In my book alone, there's hundreds and hundreds of examples. So something's changed.
listen don't fire repentance if you love me keep my commandments don't fight the
commandments for this is the love of God that we keep his commandments remember
The psychedelic hippie movement of the 1960s was conceived in a government lab
created by the CIA and this counterculture was introduced via Laurel Canyon.
The plan was to hook the kids on sex drugs and rock and roll to quell the anti-war movement.
The military and the CIA used LSD and other MK Ultra techniques to subdue the youth under a well-orchestrated promotional media campaign.
Maryfactor artists, such as Frank Zappa, Jim Morrison, Papa John Phillips, and David Crosby were children of high-ranking members of the American military and once lived in a Los Angeles neighborhood of Laurel Canyon, which also was once home to a military film studio and Air Force Station named Lookout Mountain.
During the 1960's psychedelic movement, concert venues and music festivals like Woodstock and the Trips Festival were used as laboratories for secret government mind control experiments.
But what is happening at today's concerts like the Astro World Music Festival or Coachella?
This might be the craziest thing I have ever seen, so at Lana Del Roy's concert, a wave of energy or whatever the heck happened jolted everyone in the crowd back just to watch the raw footage.
So Travis Scott's concert in Rome reportedly left 60 people injured.
Travis Scott's live debut of Utopia at the Circus Maximus in Rome has reportedly left
approximately 60 attendees injured and in need of treatment.
fear spread across Rome after people felt shaking near the historical site
Circus Maximus, but it wasn't an earthquake. It was a Travis Scott concert
and fans jumping so vigorously there that the ground shook to the equivalent
of a magnitude 1.3 earthquake. And now people are wondering if it's safe to
hold music venues at that ancient site after all that shaking. Wow. On
Wednesday, August 9th, Euro News published an article detailing an incident
at the shows.
that resulted in fans getting hurt. The news comes after the tragic events of
the rapper's infamous 2021 Astro World Festival, which left 10 people dead
following a stampede at the outdoor event.
Burning Man has a lengthy history.
It started nearly 40 years ago.
June 1986 as a small ritual on Baker Beach in San Francisco with just 20 guests.
They burned an 8 foot tall effigy.
The Burning Man 2014 105 foot tall effigy was burned.
The tallest ever that year's event drew nearly 66,000 campers.
Tragedy struck in 2017 though.
through himself into the flames of the burning monument. He died a day later.
We're not learning a man who died at Burning Man Friday was from Truckee,
the Washoe County Sheriff's Office, identifying him as 32 year old Leon
Reese. They say that he was found unresponsive on the festival grounds
Friday and declared dead onside by first responders. While the cause of his
death is still under investigation, the medical examiner says drug intoxication
is suspected in this case.
22 years ago, Frank Olson plunged to his death from the 10th floor of the hotel statler in New York.
His family was told he'd committed suicide.
It wasn't until June 11th this year that his family learned that in fact he'd unwittingly participated in a CIA drug experiment that resulted in his bizarre death.
It was here that the CIA funded a series of experiments, severe experiments, brain surgery,
psychosurgery, creation of amnesia, parapsychology, manipulation of genes, administration of
sodium penithal, hypnosis, isolation, and deprivation of sleep.
A report of a woman who had electrodes implanted in the brain and was then given LSD and other
drugs.
Lapsed into a trance-like state, the work was done by the Institute's then director, Dr. Ewan Cameron.
It is the closest experimentation to brainwashing yet disclosed.
The search for the Manchurian candidate, a history of intelligence agency work with mind control.
All the scientific data get logical mind-altering experiments is now being utilized to condition
the susceptible subconscious minds of children so the next generation will already be pre-programmed
to embrace the totality of the Luciferian doctrine.
It's morning again. The sun is shining. The goats are screaming.
And I'm still here, despite the fact that last night,
I witnessed someone get ritualistically murdered
by my dad's cult that I just inherited.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, friends.
What's up?
Ah!
I'm Petey.
I had it all.
Mother!
Here.
What's this?
It's a message from your father.
Here's me, your father.
The community of New Utopia is all yours.
Travis Scott's live debut of utopia at the Circus Maximus in Rome
Who are you the names the Mona?
Sidekick has arrived. I don't need to say every villain needs a sidekick. I'm not a villain
The real villain is still out there, and I do need help
I can help you but promise me you won't freak out. Why would I trust you? I promise even when you see the horn
This is the part where you run.
They call me hell!
They call me Stingy Stingy!
Let's break stuff.
The Reprobate Mind
Now, Disney, the company that lost at least $300 million dollars, are promoting homosexuality
in the animated kids movies Lightyear and Strange World, is at it again.
Courtney Faber posted videos on TikTok of her family's visit to Disneyland.
One of them has received 8 million views.
It shows her daughter greeted by Nick.
My name's Nick.
I want to pray God bless.
Apprentices, I'm here to shop around and make all these selections for the day.
Mommy, why does that princess have a mustache?
Oh, honey, because some princesses are boys.
A new show about an 18-year-old impregnated by Satan.
That's Disney's latest project.
They've agreed to stream the six-part German produced series on Disney Plus.
The show's name is Pauline.
It's produced by the same people who created the Netflix show
How to Sell Drugs Online, Fast.
The producers say Pauline is close to their hearts.
They're thrilled that Disney loves the coming-of-age story as much as we do.
The spellcasters just want to plant the seeds of confusion.
Hasatan will water it with the unholy water of deception so the weeds, thorns, and tears
can overtake and choke the good fruit from the heart of the child.
Autobot Scepticon Terran, he wants to destroy us all!
Autobots, defend this home with everything you've got!
Transformers EarthSpark.
Stream new episodes with your family July 28th, exclusively on Paramount Plus.
My pronouns are they, them.
You already know that
Hey, I believe
I'm safe when I'm with my friends or other non-binary people
non-binary
People who aren't email or mail. Oh, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have assume. I always knew my pronouns felt right
What a wonderful word for a wonderful experience
When the spirit of confusion takes hold of a generation,
they have little to no defense against the deception of a predator.
I've trained all the children at my summer camp to come to me whenever I play my recorder.
A bunch of 5 to 11 year olds are just following me wherever I go.
I have so much power and I love it. It's the perfect time to teach them about trends.
Now, you see, over time, the actual people of the nation
begin to take on the attributes and personality traits of the demon gods they knowingly are
Pan, our Peter Pan, the Pied Piper, is clearly manifesting not only in this individual, but
throughout Western society.
There's no such thing as someone else's child.
No such thing as someone else's child.
That's a really bad idea. Now I want you to pay close attention. Watch how the
Satanic media covers for the transgender agenda in this next report.
First responders were called here to these apartments on Saturday for an
apparent cardiac arrest. When they got here, they discovered someone had died
and also found that several people were hiding children in a back room.
Tonight, four children less than 10 years old are in DCF custody after
authorities and public officials say they were found in an apartment with
six cross-dressing men, sex toys, drugs and alcohol. Firefighters discovered
them after one of those adults died at the apartment. According to their
incident report, the apartment was in extreme unsanitary conditions. All
adult parties were being uncooperative and denied having children in the
apartment.
drugs, alcohol, drug paraphernalia, sex toys, etc.
Did you catch that? Six cross-dressing men, not transgender women.
They want you to know men, evil men did this.
Not their stunning and brave transgender women
who are part of their loving LGBT plus community.
They even broke their own rule and misgendered them by referring to them as men.
Tonight, four children less than 10 years old are in DCF custody.
After authorities and public officials say they were found in an apartment with six cross-dressing men,
sex toys, drugs and alcohol.
Hey, it's okay.
I don't want to say it when I'm with my friends or other non-binary people.
Non-binary.
People who aren't you know
The poll published in Newsweek is found that 44% of Millennials believe misgendering somebody should be a criminal offense
the reprobate mind
I haven't where we've never been
Because of the growing repentance of the chosen elect,
the vengeance which belongs only to Yahua is being activated
and our enemies are falling on their own sword.
To me belongeth vengeance and recompense. Their foot shall slide in due time, for the day of their calamity is at hand, and the things that shall come upon them make haste.
Though a spirit of confusion within their ranks has caused them lots of friendly fire and lots of collateral damage, but the excess deaths are still going up.
Their main target is still the children of Israel.
Finland's Minister for Economic Affairs Veilam said addressing the parliament quote it would
be justified for Finland to shoulder its responsibility by promoting climate abortion.
Climate abortion would be a small step for a person but a giant leap for humanity.
He said the solution.
Shalom family.
And what wisdom is in them?
As a percentage of humanity's so-called best and brightest have their lights pharmacologically dimmed.
Their pride and glory was once their IQ, but now they find themselves on the spectrum, crippled by cognitive function on a steep decline.
Notice that you've been more forgetful than usual lately.
Researchers think they know the reason why,
and they say it might have something to do
with the COVID-19 pandemic.
Here's Brandy Smith.
Why could the COVID-19 pandemic cause brain inflammation in people who never caught the virus?
Since the start of the coronavirus pandemic, reports of psychological distress, fatigue,
and brain fog increased significantly, even among people never infected.
So what's causing these results?
Well, the one thing that we see is that this is a widespread problem.
The memory issues, the confusion, the brain fog.
behavior, a movie of mystery, power, and suspense.
Clear and unnatural picture begins to form in our mind.
They're going to strap me into some chair and go for a little bit of my grace.
Would you just wait a minute and listen to me?
Two sessions, two days, a hundred bucks a day.
I'll power up the bottles.
Oh, he's just wondering.
Are you doing anything tonight?
Oh, it's him.
He's dead.
And the dead don't come back and take revenge.
Somebody help me!
We've heard your views on our work in the past, Mr. Brady.
You're the crap for somebody else.
You got a list of people in the program.
Now, just relax, Pete.
It'll be over in no time.
It's done.
All over again.
Let me go! Let me go!
Mr. Brady, I see you've found your way.
Peter, you ready?
The choice is yours, Mr. Brady.
Either give him a gun or shoot him. The choice is yours, Mr. Brady.
Oh Jesus.
What did you do to my kid? What did you do?
Strange behavior.
Their pseudo-scientific leaders and the strict adherence to a materialist, atheistic worldview
has not served them well in this critical time of decision.
professing themselves to be wise, they became fools.
So, it turns out, that survival of the fittest and natural selection favor those with the
spiritual discernment to perceive a fork-tongue serpent disguised as a trusted expert authority.
So once again, the set-apart children of Abba Yahua are vindicated.
We emerge with our temples genetically unscathed with our creators original biological design still intact
Wendy Williams says there's no way she's getting vaccinated Dr. Oz tries to persuade her during an appearance on his show
Are you planning on getting your back seat now? No, no, I don't trust it
I've never gotten the flu shot either, though,
and you and I have talked about that.
And several of the doctors on my team
talked to me about, Wendy, we'll get the flu shot.
I've never had the flu, I'm not getting a flu shot.
I very rarely get a cold.
I never have headaches.
I don't take an aspirin because I feel my heart murmur
or something like that.
I'm not getting, no, I don't trust it.
There, I said it.
I don't trust it.
I disagree. I think the vaccine is safe.
So are there questions that I can answer for you
about the vaccine that might make you more comfortable?
I'm just...
No.
None.
You doctors, you talk a lot of focus, focus to me.
And I go home and I think about it,
and then I come up with my own decision,
because only I know, ultimately, what's best for me.
Listen, 10 million people and more have the flu vaccine,
and how many people per year catch the flu?
You know, I, no, I'm not getting the vaccine, Dr. Oz.
I'm not.
I don't trust it.
And is there something in particular
you don't trust about it,
the fact that it was made quickly,
the fact that we don't have enough follow-up?
What specifically is bothering you about it?
Doctors are really smart people,
but doctors don't know everything
and that's been proven as well.
I'm not getting the vaccine.
I think maybe we should come over for dinner
and we should talk a little bit.
What do you think?
Nope.
No, could you put the vaccine, I'm going to come back from the bathroom and feel something stick me in the booty, and that would have been you.
She knows me.
I was stunned and flabbergasted when she told me that she wasn't going to get vaccinated.
One commentator called her remarks incredibly ignorant and destructive.
We know Misery loves company.
In the altered know, they cannot recruit the righteous of Israel, so they go after the
rotten figs, the low-hanging fruit.
Those who may have a sense of right and wrong, but they love money, and they don't want
to lose the glamour and glitz, or whatever they've acquired in this rebablon, so they
let strangers stick something in their body for money, resulting in strange behavior.
but they are all really just here run of the mill,
garden variety, whores of Babylon.
Speaking of the Vax, Wendy Williams has tested positive
for the virus and this has prompted the new season
of her daytime talk show to be delayed to October.
The show's official Instagram account shared a post yesterday
and they revealed that Wendy contracted a breakthrough case,
which means that the TV personality got sick
despite being vaccinated.
The show account also share the due to this, Wendy would need time to quarantine and fully
recover for a safe production environment. The Wendy Williams show is coming to an end,
unfortunately. Yeah, producers say that the cancellations is a result of Williams ongoing
health issues. So guests have been filling in for her since
the last I should say been filling in for her since she last hosted in July.
And there's more, including reports that Wendy was voluntarily admitted to a
New York hospital for psychiatric evaluation. Strange behavior, breaking
entertainment news comedian Gilbert Godfrey, who had one of the most well
known voices in Hollywood has died.
Good afternoon. This is the KTLA 5 News at 1. I'm Glenn Walker and I'm Lou Parker. Godfrey's family announced his passing on Twitter
Godfrey died from a rare genetic muscle disorder that affects the heart his publicist and longtime friend told the Associated Press. In addition to being a stand-up comedian
Godfrey was also known for voice acting and television and film including as the voice of Iago the parrot and Disney's Aladdin
Godfrey was 67 years old
Jeffrey Ross called me and said Bob Saget had died and I I remember I was like
thought it was a sick joke and I was waiting for the punchline. I went to the
pharmacy the other day I got a booster shot and I should have gotten it in my
arm but I got it in my butt so I'm a little pain but
Tonight, police releasing new details and 911 calls from comedian Bob Saget's final
moments. And autopsy revealed the 65-year-old had died of trauma to the back of his head.
This comedian Heather McDonald is out of a valley hospital tonight after she
collapsed over the weekend during a show at the Tempe Improv.
She spoke with team 12's Colleen Socorra today about the frightening tumble and Colleen how is she doing?
Her management saying she suffered a skull fracture in the fall.
I'm really you know just recovering from hitting the back of my head really hard because I just went like...
Timber comedian Bob Saget's final moments and autopsy revealed the 65-year-old had died of trauma to the back of his head. I
Don't mean to brag. I don't care, but I want you to know double-vaxxed
booster flu shot and
I'm gonna be honest. I have the shingle shot too
And I still get my period what yes
Traveled, went to Mexico twice, did shows, meet and greets, never got COVID, clearly.
Jesus loves me the most. Seriously. So nice. So nice.
St. Clair County Emergency Management Agency Director Herb Simmons is getting creative to try and get more people to get their COVID-19 vaccine.
Hi, this is Gilbert Gottfried with an important message.
St. Clair County is running a COVID-19 mass vaccination site at the Bell Clair Fairgrounds.
a magical matrimony to sickness and health pop superstar Justin Bieber by his
wife Haley side after she was rushed to the hospital. The wife and model
posting on her Instagram. I was sitting at breakfast with my husband when I
started having stroke like symptoms. It sounds like if she was diagnosed with
a clot in the brain, that sounds like they made a diagnosis of stroke at 25
years old. That's rare. The majority of patients are 78 years old.
neurosurgeon and professor with USC Dr. Matthew Tenser says only about 10% of
stroke patients are somebody less than 50. They're caused by blood clots
traveling to the brain than cutting off oxygen.
without seeing Haley's medical records.
Tenser can't know for sure,
but says it looks like she did everything right.
It sounds like as soon as the symptoms started,
they called 911 and she was evaluated in the hospital
right away, which is exactly the right thing to do.
Signs are sudden onset symptoms of numbness or vision loss
on one side of the body,
inability to speak, dizziness,
and a massive stroke could be devastating.
that the disembodied spirits that inhabit the waters of the earth desire a new body,
similar to the one they had before the great destruction of the old world.
Similar to how Epstein turned Little Saint James into his own perverted
playground, Diddy would take women to the Caribbean on yachts where there was
alleged illicit activity.
Very first time.
Yeah, I have an island.
This is just for inspirational motivation and use it on me.
You don't know a lot of black men that come from the hood.
They got an island.
I got an island called Love Island.
And then you realize that, you know, the plane landed and then we had the float to
another island. What was going through your head when we were going there?
Nygard owns homes all over the world, including this huge estate in the Bahamas,
where he's entertained Britain's Prince Andrew.
Little Saint James off the coast of Saint Thomas was privately owned by Epstein,
and you can only get to this island by helicopter or private boat.
It's 73 acres of pure paradise.
Necker is one of the British Virgin Islands.
And for Sir Richard Branson, founder and CEO
of the Virgin Group, it's the place he calls home.
The Virgin Group
They say love is blind.
Blind.
Shalom family.
Just to...
Blindness.
Feel it.
Well, I guess they've decided to thin the herd.
They say love is blind.
Blind.
So there go the masses,
like sheep to the slaughter.
Blindly stumbling past all the red flags,
sleepwalking
right into their trap.
Stop home syndrome.
Some were cursed to be blind.
The Lord shall smite thee with madness and blindness and astonishment of heart, and thou
shall to grope that noonday as the blind grope it in darkness.
Others are programmed to be blind.
We once were blind, but now we can see, and now we're desperately fighting to remove the blindfold from off the eyes of as many brothers and sisters as possible.
Against great spiritual opposition, through Yah's grace, and the fervent prayers of our supporters, we were able to release Marine Kingdom 3.
But we could have never anticipated what we would uncover
The spawning grounds for the elites most ambitious grand conspiracy
Which brings us to our latest presentation the elite secret treasure exposed blood rituals hidden in plain sight
This video is another important piece of the puzzle
As we move closer to finishing out the final chapter in our Marine Kingdom saga,
the enemy is seeing red and is now activating the pre-programming they secretly place
in the subconscious minds of certain segments of society.
You're about to see Channing Tatum like you've never seen him before.
In his new thriller, Blink Twice.
Blink Twice.
Channing in the role of tech billionaire Slater King.
A mysterious tech billionaire, Channing himself described as absolutely bonkers.
I forgot you're on your own island.
It's casual.
So casual, yeah.
It's nice to meet you.
Come on, it's very, very cute.
We gotta go.
Tracks.
Here we go.
We need to be in a place where I can get an umbrella in my drink.
It's nice to meet you, freedom.
We're going to my island for a few days.
When a server at a benefit clicks with a young billionaire, he beckons her to join his revelers
on an island of indulgence, where she soon senses that behind that tech bro charm might
be something horrific.
How do you get into character for something like that?
It's almost impossible to explain in a way because I really had to create something so wildly esoteric.
It's so wildly esoteric.
If I explained the weird things, the weird little doom compartments in my brain to make this person operate.
Yeah, it's a wild way. I was reading a lot of Carl Jung and just going into the shadow.
Just really strange stuff.
That's why I said, I'm in danger.
Well, maybe not the other side, but I'll answer that one, right?
Naomi, among the emotions you have to play is, during flashbacks, extreme trauma.
Yeah.
What was that like for you?
It was, it was, it was hard.
Like, there is a thing about, like, acting the same way, where, like, you know, it's not real.
but like your body doesn't.
Now, Amazon MGM, Steven, this is really important,
released a trigger warning this week
ahead of the release,
so I basically get ahead of all of this,
saying that they are alerting viewers
to depictions of sexual violence and abuse in this film.
Where the trauma and the terror
feel ripped from the headlines reel.
What are we gonna do about you?
Me too, Epstein, the convictions of Harvey Weinstein, how much of all those things affected what the final product is.
Toward the end of the film is revealed that the character Slater King himself is merely a puppet
who has also been subjected to artificially induced amnesia and mind control.
In fact, the entire island is a secret staging ground for clandestine mind control and sexual
experiments conducted by shadowy higher-ups.
While this film mirrors real-world events in many ways, Slater came, let's talk about
the island.
I just disconnect, no work.
Phone please, wait for real?
It's just better without phones.
Excuse me, I need the phones, guys. I need your phones.
I need your phones, I need your phones.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
And Quincy, I know you have two phones, Quincy.
Oh, there you go. That's what I love.
Really?
Yeah.
While this film mirrors real-world events in many ways, it still manages to conveniently
leave out the true purpose of these large-scale sex trafficking operations strategically placed
on remote Caribbean islands.
And that's because the social engineers behind this movie want to divert the audience's attention
by framing these billionaire sex islands as just another hashtag me too moment.
Though the general public sees the Caribbean Islands as solely a vacation destination full of sun, crystal water and good times, for the majority of the full-time residents of these islands, life is far from a vacation.
While exact figures vary, the majority of the Caribbean population is of African descent.
In many Caribbean countries, the black population constitutes over 70% of the total population,
making Afro-Caribbeans the dominant ethnic group in the region.
Filing of their holy temples.
A new trailer for the Little Mermaid is generating extraordinary reaction, especially among black girls.
She's black!
Oh look, a black mermaid!
She's like me!
Many of them are mesmerized, watching a cherished fairytale character who looks just like them.
22-year-old actress Hallie Bailey stars as Ariel in Disney's new live-action film.
And all she has to do is look at the excitement of the little girls embracing her.
She's black!
To subconsciously consent to the defiling of their holy temples.
to show you how they subliminally tell you bit by bit, knowing most are unable to decipher
their signs and symbols and connect the dots.
creatures born. The first plug-in hybrid V-12 engine.
Sean Combs served as brand ambassador for Siroc, netting him over $60 million a year. But when
the All About the Benjamin's rapper and record executive decided to sue Siroc's parent company,
Diageo, for racial discrimination, he inadvertently positioned himself
In direct opposition to some of the oldest, most powerful and dangerous, European aristocratic
family dynasties known to man, Saurak is a brand under the ownership of Diageo, which
is in turn owned by the Guinness family, notably...
Anita Patience Guinness from the Guinness family solidified an alliance with the Rothschild
Bank and Dynasty through marriage to Amshelmaire James Rothschild, establishing a blood connection
between the two blue-blooded families.
In January 2023, Sir Ivan Meninez, the CEO of Diageo, was bestowed the Royal Knighthood
by King Charles of England.
This significant event coincided with Diddy's lawsuit and subsequent downfall.
You have the experience with major corporations, like me, my particular experience with Beam Centauri, it was great in the beginning.
It's great for us to work for them. It is not so cool when you start to own things.
You see what I'm saying? So I made a lot of money with them too.
There's a point, they did a deal that mirrored what Puffy's deal with Diageo was for Saraw. So he didn't have ownership.
at any point, but he was getting a lot of money, like almost like $60 million a year at one point.
So you see him go to daily on is when you see him have some issues. And these people have
really strong relationships. Don't think that the civil case doesn't turn into a criminal case
He's making that them uncomfortable. That's a big part of it the spirits businesses. It's not governed
They got a discus board that they created right if you got two companies did a three billion now
I mean, the glaring hole is that the indictment goes after sort of the bottom of what we learned
from the Lil Rod lawsuit, goes after the guns and the drugs and a lot of the violence on
Diddy's level.
But notably missing is the name Lucian Grange, the CEO of Universal Music Group.
A legend, clear evidence of him knowing about the parties and funding the parties, but
later on, through mechanisms of power, he got his name removed from that lawsuit, is
my understanding, and now he does not show up in the indictment against Diddy.
You see.
The misguided and perverse Israelite P. Diddy, with all his business-savvy and eagle-driven
ambition, miscalculated his importance to the sore-wielding Edomite power structure,
and was given a quick reality check by his Luciferian overlords, who effortlessly removed
the rapper's protection and untouchable status, leaving him vulnerable and exposed to the
but I feel like he might be the scapegoat here. And the goal is to try to keep it, stop it with him.
Nothing more to see here. Don't go any higher. Don't look at how dirty and deeply this goes.
Is that your sense of it?
They're going to cover up all of the connections and not go after the bigger fish
and use Diddy's escape goat. And that seems likely based on past history.
P. Diddy has always been a puppet of Clive Davis and his social engineering overlords
Clive Davis is the bisexual Jewish record exact who facilitated and funded P. Diddy's label bad boy records
Bad boy records was used to start the little baby boy program little seeds
Bad boy, little Wayne little dirt little gotty little John little scrappy
No, we can't forget Sada baby baby
It's clear
Clive Davis handpicked P. Diddy because of his degenerate proclivities and willingness to endure the elites degrading initiation rights
Star Island, like where P. Diddy stays or throw his freak off sack.
The disgraced sexual deviant P. Diddy was merely a curator and supplier trafficking people
as human merchandise to the royal houses, to the royal houses.
We explore these connections in detail and our latest patreon exclusive
to see the flame but envy was the price of fame and now he stands where the echoes fall
with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to venom in the same breath said
but the fire in his eyes burns gold